<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tlocrt</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/</link><description>Recent content on tlocrt</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlocrt.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Now</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/now/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/now/</guid><description>These days, I am:
Trying to find LEDs to add to the back of a painting. Working on a music video for Bitesized. Designing a dress. Looking to incorporate more analogue tech in music production.</description></item><item><title>Life of a plant</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/life_of_a_plant/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/life_of_a_plant/</guid><description>We have a big pretty plant (of the Scindapsus pictus kind I think). One day, after spotting one of its leaves that had fallen off, I felt inspired to paint something plant-related.
I found the combination of bright greens in younger leaves, the deep dark greens in mature ones, and the yellowish-brown colour of an occasional dead leaf interesting. Since I had three canvases, I tried painting something resembling three stages of a plant&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>tank top</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/tank_top/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/tank_top/</guid><description>My mum was visiting and I made her a tank top. She wanted a tank top with longer sides, similar to one she already has.
The most challenging part of this project was the bottom hem. Since the sides are longer, the bottom edges were not perpendicular to the side seam. I had to improvise sewing those corners, but they turned out not too bad.
Here&amp;rsquo;s one more pic.</description></item><item><title>Website</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/website/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/website/</guid><description>This website was created in Hugo. Since I&amp;rsquo;m a web development noob, it took a small eternity. But it was fun!
What you&amp;rsquo;re seeing is a custom Hugo theme, developed by following the first ~1/3 of the helpful book Build Websites with Hugo by Brian P. Hogan and then freestyling (aka typing semi-coherent questions into various search engines and LLMs until something started working).
Features Features that took way more time than they should have and that probably nobody else will pay any attention to include:</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 08:53:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/about/</guid><description>During the working hours, I think about maths. Some of what I like to do during the non-working hours is documented here.
To see what I&amp;rsquo;m up to, check out my now page.
If you want to contact me, you can do so by sending an email to hi at the domain of this website.</description></item><item><title>MIDI Keyboard Case</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/midi_keyboard_case/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/midi_keyboard_case/</guid><description>I had been on a passive lookout for a portable MIDI keyboard for quite some time. When I saw the beautiful Arturia MiniLab 3 Alpine White, I knew that was the one.
Since I wanted to be able to take it places and since I had some curtain leftovers its beauty had to be protected at all costs, I decided to make a soft case for it.
The biggest challenge in the design process was figuring out how to deal with the protruding knobs and faders.</description></item><item><title>Change of scene</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/music/change_of_scene/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/music/change_of_scene/</guid><description/></item><item><title>noise</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/digital_art/noise/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/digital_art/noise/</guid><description>At some point, I stumbled upon the gorgeous animations created by Bleuje. According to the FAQ on the website, the animations were created in Processing, so I was inspired to try it out.
Noise is the third idea I tried (and the first one I thought looked kinda cool).
It was a fun little project and it increased my appreciation for what Bleuje is doing by 1000x.
Below is the code I used for Noise.</description></item><item><title>ghosting</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/digital_art/ghosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/digital_art/ghosting/</guid><description>After Skyscrapers, I kept experimenting with gradients. Ghosting was the result.
(The title comes from ghosting in photography, not in real life.)</description></item><item><title>skyscrapers</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/digital_art/skyscrapers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/digital_art/skyscrapers/</guid><description>I was trying to make a gradient for an unrelated project and I liked how two overlapping rectangles looked like.
After some tweaking of the positions and the colours, Skyscrapers were born.</description></item><item><title>Patch Shirt</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/patch_shirt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/patch_shirt/</guid><description>This is the first item of clothing I made.
It was also the most challenging sewing project so far. I had never worked with stretchy fabrics before and I don&amp;rsquo;t have a walking foot, so it took some trial and error before I was able to get anything resembling a &amp;ldquo;straight&amp;rdquo; zig-zag stitch.
I also had a small accident while I was sewing a hem, which resulted in a small hole.</description></item><item><title>Mountains</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/mountains/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/mountains/</guid><description>The crackle paste strikes again in this one &amp;mdash; this time only in the snow-mode, though. I had also discovered the masking tape at this point, hence the sharp edges in the mountain peaks.</description></item><item><title>Dissociate (Acoustic)</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/videos/dissociate_acoustic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/videos/dissociate_acoustic/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Pocket in a Pocket</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/pocket_in_a_pocket/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/pocket_in_a_pocket/</guid><description>I have a backpack that is lacking inner pockets and pen holders. The pocket-in-a-pocket solves this issue.
It can also easily be moved to a different bag, together with all its contents.</description></item><item><title>Brush Roll</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/brush_roll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/brush_roll/</guid><description>I needed somewhere to store my paintbrushes, so I created a brush roll out of some curtain leftovers and towel ties.
Here it is in its rolled-up state.</description></item><item><title>Desert winter</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/desert_winter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/desert_winter/</guid><description>I like textures in paintings and I recently got some crackle paste.
In its usual dry state, the crackle paste looks kind of like a desert floor that hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen the rain in a very long time. I also realised I could make the paste into a different kind of texture if I poked it before it dried. This made me think of snow.
The result of this little experimentation was this painting.</description></item><item><title>Isolating Causes</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/music/isolating_causes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/music/isolating_causes/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Begin</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/music/begin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/music/begin/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Lofoten</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/photography/lofoten/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/photography/lofoten/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Graubünden</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/photography/graubuenden/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/photography/graubuenden/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Better Times</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/music/better_times/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/music/better_times/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Berlin</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/photography/berlin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/photography/berlin/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Dissociate</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/music/dissociate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/music/dissociate/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>