<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Paintings on tlocrt</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/</link><description>Recent content in Paintings on tlocrt</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Life of a plant</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/life_of_a_plant/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/life_of_a_plant/</guid><description>We have a big pretty plant (of the Scindapsus pictus kind I think). One day, after spotting one of its leaves that had fallen off, I felt inspired to paint something plant-related.
I found the combination of bright greens in younger leaves, the deep dark greens in mature ones, and the yellowish-brown colour of an occasional dead leaf interesting. Since I had three canvases, I decided to try to paint something resembling three stages of a plant&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>Mountains</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/mountains/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/mountains/</guid><description>The crackle paste strikes again in this one &amp;mdash; this time only in the snow-mode, though. I had also discovered the masking tape at this point, hence the sharp edges in the mountain peaks.</description></item><item><title>Desert winter</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/desert_winter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/visual/paintings/desert_winter/</guid><description>I like textures in paintings and I recently got some crackle paste.
In its usual dry state, the crackle paste looks kind of like a desert floor that hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen the rain in a very long time. I also realised I could make the paste into a different kind of texture if I poked it before it dried. This mode made me think of snow.
I felt like combining the two thoughts and this little experimentation concluded with the creation of this painting.</description></item></channel></rss>