<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sewing on tlocrt</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/</link><description>Recent content in Sewing on tlocrt</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>tank top</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/tank_top/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/tank_top/</guid><description>My mum was visiting and I made her a tank top. She wanted a tank top with longer sides, similar to one she already has.
The most challenging part of this project was the bottom hem. Since the sides are longer, the bottom edges were not perpendicular to the side seam. I had to improvise sewing those corners, but they turned out not too bad.
Here&amp;rsquo;s one more pic.</description></item><item><title>MIDI Keyboard Case</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/midi_keyboard_case/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/midi_keyboard_case/</guid><description>I had been on a passive lookout for a portable MIDI keyboard for quite some time. When I saw the beautiful Arturia MiniLab 3 Alpine White, I knew that was the one.
Since I wanted to be able to take it places and since I had some curtain leftovers its beauty had to be protected, I decided to make a soft case for it.
The biggest challenge in the design process was figuring out how to deal with the protruding knobs and faders.</description></item><item><title>Patch Shirt</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/patch_shirt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/patch_shirt/</guid><description>This is the first item of clothing I made.
It was also the most challenging sewing project so far. I had never worked with stretchy fabrics before and I don&amp;rsquo;t have a walking foot, so it took some trial and error before I was able to get anything resembling a &amp;ldquo;straight&amp;rdquo; zig-zag stitch.
I also had a small accident while I was sewing a hem, which resulted in a small hole.</description></item><item><title>Pocket in a Pocket</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/pocket_in_a_pocket/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/pocket_in_a_pocket/</guid><description>I have a backpack that is lacking inner pockets and pen holders. The pocket-in-a-pocket solves this issue.
It can also easily be moved to a different bag, together with all its contents.</description></item><item><title>Brush Roll</title><link>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/brush_roll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlocrt.com/other/sewing/brush_roll/</guid><description>I needed somewhere to store my paintbrushes, so I created a brush roll out of some curtain leftovers and towel ties.
Here it is in its rolled-up state.</description></item></channel></rss>