<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sewing on tlocrt</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sewing on tlocrt</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MIDI Keyboard Case</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/midi_keyboard_case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/midi_keyboard_case/</guid>
      <description>I had been on a passive lookout for a portable MIDI keyboard for quite some time. When I saw the beautiful Arturia MiniLab 3 Alpine White, I knew that was the one.&#xA;Since I wanted to be able to take it places and since I had some curtain leftovers its beauty had to be protected at all costs, I decided to make a soft case for it.&#xA;The biggest challenge in the design process was figuring out how to deal with the protruding knobs and faders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Shirt</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/patch_shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/patch_shirt/</guid>
      <description>This is the first item of clothing I made.&#xA;It was also the most challenging sewing project so far. I had never worked with stretchy fabrics before and I don&amp;rsquo;t have a walking foot, so it took some trial and error before I was able to get anything resembling a &amp;ldquo;straight&amp;rdquo; zig-zag stitch.&#xA;I also had a small accident while I was sewing a hem, which resulted in a small hole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pocket in a Pocket</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/pocket_in_a_pocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/pocket_in_a_pocket/</guid>
      <description>I have a backpack that is lacking inner pockets and pen holders. The pocket-in-a-pocket solves this issue.&#xA;It can also easily be moved to a different bag, together with all its contents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brush Roll</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/brush_roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/other/sewing/brush_roll/</guid>
      <description>I needed somewhere to store my paintbrushes, so I created a brush roll out of some curtain leftovers and towel ties.&#xA;Here it is in its rolled-up state.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
